They say in the town of Widdershade, people don't cast shadows after sunset.
It's not magic.
It's Felix.
Felix Holloway wasn't always a shadow collector.
He started out as a quiet cobbler with bad eyesight and a worse memory.
But one cloudy evening, while fixing a boot by candlelight, he noticed something odd - the customer's shadow stepped away from him.
It yawned, stretched, and disappeared out the window.
Felix blinked.
Twice.
Then did what any sane man would: he followed it.
He chased the shadow through cobbled alleys, up a twisted oak tree, and into a hole behind the apothecary, where - to his absolute confusion - he found a market.
Not for fruit.
Not for shoes.
But for shadows.
Tall ones, crooked ones, shadows that danced when you whistled - all hanging on clotheslines, whispering like curtains in the wind.
A woman with silver eyes traded hers for twenty extra years of sleep.
A butcher sold his to forget the war.
Felix, as it turns out, had a gift.
He could untie a shadow from your feet like untying a shoelace.
It made him...
popular.
By the time the moon was high, he'd bought a shadow that told jokes, one that could open locked doors, and another that kept perfect time like a metronome.
Years passed.
Felix became a legend.
People lined up to lighten their burdens.
To sell the parts of themselves they no longer wanted to carry in the light.
But one day, a girl came to him and said, "I want yours." He laughed.
"Mine?
It's stubborn.
Doesn't even follow me properly anymore." "I don't need it to follow," she said.
"Just to remember." Felix was quiet.
For the first time, he looked behind him - and saw nothing.
Just a trail of old footsteps.
And then he realized...
He hadn't seen his shadow in years.